<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Basic Developer Skills on Learn Forever</title>
    <link>http://blog.hakanserce.com/categories/basic-developer-skills/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Basic Developer Skills on Learn Forever</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:00:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.hakanserce.com/categories/basic-developer-skills/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Learn Touch Typing: a Guide for Seasoned Hunt and Pecker</title>
      <link>http://blog.hakanserce.com/post/how-to-learn-touch-typing-a-guide-for-seasoned-hunt-and-pecker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:00:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.hakanserce.com/post/how-to-learn-touch-typing-a-guide-for-seasoned-hunt-and-pecker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://blog.hakanserce.com/img/hunt-and-peck.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;/img/hunt-and-peck.jpg&#34; title=&#34;/img/hunt-and-peck.jpg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learning touch typing is a lot more challenging for a seasoned hunt-and-pecker. Years and years of acquired habits are difficult to unlearn. Additionally, having daily tasks to keep up while learning to touch type, and the fact that initially touch typing is even slower than hunt-and-peck style doesn&#39;t help with the situation. However, following a disciplined process can alleviate most of the difficulties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Programmers Actually Need Touch Typing?</title>
      <link>http://blog.hakanserce.com/post/do-programmers-actually-need-touch-typing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 16:04:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.hakanserce.com/post/do-programmers-actually-need-touch-typing/</guid>
      <description>Touch typing (also called touch type or touch keyboarding) is typing without using the sense of sight to find the keys. Specifically, a touch typist will know their location on the keyboard through muscle memory. (Wikipedia)  After about 20 years of programming with hunt and peck style shamelessly, I decided to learn touch typing a few months ago. I&#39;ll talk about why I decided to learn touch typing at the end of this post, but I first want to spend time on the critical question: &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>